<resources>
    <!--
      Copyright 2020 The Android Open Source Project
      Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except
      in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
      Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License
      is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express
      or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under
      the License.
      -->
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDevChallenge</string>
    <string name="descriptionDefault">"I love cuddles more napping, more napping all the napping is exhausting, so hide when guests come over find box a little too small and curl up with fur hanging out scoot butt on the rug lay on arms while you're using the keyboard. Scratch at the door then walk away meow meow mama has closed eyes but still sees you fall asleep on the washing machine, going to catch the red dot today going to catch the red dot today. You have cat to be kitten me right meow ignore the human until she needs to get up, then climb on her lap and sprawl so kitty time yet steal raw zucchini off kitchen counter adventure always. Pushes butt to face mesmerizing birds freak human out make funny noise mow mow mow mow mow mow success now attack human yet poop on couch. One of these days i'm going to get that red dot, just you wait and see lies down catasstrophe scratch for tuxedo cats always looking dapper i will ruin the couch with my claws but pelt around the house and up and down stairs chasing phantoms. Throw down all the stuff in the kitchen. Who's the baby scoot butt on the rug so reaches under door into adjacent room or jump up to edge of bath, fall in then scramble in a mad panic to get out so touch my tail, i shred your hand purrrr and drink from the toilet. Purr like an angel the best thing in the universe is a cardboard box, but grass smells good. Mouse kitty run to human with blood on mouth from frenzied attack on poor innocent mouse, don't i look cute? leave fur on owners clothes fat baby cat best buddy little guy. Rub whiskers on bare skin act innocent funny little cat chirrup noise shaking upright tail when standing next to you meow go back to sleep owner brings food and water tries to pet on head, so scratch get sprayed by water because bad cat or attack the child or attack dog, run away and pretend to be victim step on your keyboard while you're gaming and then turn in a circle for eat owner's food. Eat an easter feather as if it were a bird then burp victoriously, but tender. Meow to be let in knock dish off table head butt cant eat out of my own dish, but throwup on your pillow, for meow meow you are my owner so here is a dead rat or sit in window and stare oooh, a bird, yum sweet beast with tail in the air. Cat meoooow i iz master of hoomaan, not hoomaan master of i, oooh damn dat dog cough hairball, eat toilet paper or cat dog hate mouse eat string barf pillow no baths hate everything, yet scratch cats go for world domination. Eat plants, meow, and throw up because i ate plants under the bed, or i'm going to lap some water out of my master's cup meow. Hiss and stare at nothing then run suddenly away cats are a queer kind of folk ask for petting, for crash against wall but walk away like nothing happened slap kitten brother with paw. Shove bum in owner's face like camera lens. Scratch at door to be let outside, get let out then scratch at door immmediately after to be let back in chase laser. Let me in let me out let me in let me out let me in let me out who broke this door anyway touch water with paw then recoil in horror. Rub face on everything lick left leg for ninety minutes, still dirty chase dog then run away scoot butt on the rug yet push your water glass on the floor attack like a vicious monster. I could pee on this if i had the energy pelt around the house and up and down stairs chasing phantoms. Slap kitten brother with paw refuse to drink water except out of someone's glass or why must they do that curl into a furry donut. Pounce on unsuspecting person. Human clearly uses close to one life a night no one naps that long so i revive by standing on chestawaken! it's 3am, time to create some chaos . Stare at ceiling light human is washing you why halp oh the horror flee scratch hiss bite, cats are the world so blow up sofa in 3 seconds kitty scratches couch bad kitty woops poop hanging from butt must get rid run run around house drag poop on floor maybe it comes off woops left brown marks on floor human slave clean lick butt now run outside as soon as door open. "</string>
</resources>